Guide to the New York Produce Exchange Records 1860-1955 MS 449
New-York Historical Society
- Bonded Grain Futures Market documents, 1926-1937 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 12)
  Documents include: application to and approval from the U.S. Department of Agriculture to become a Contract Market under the Grain Futures Act; subsequent related correspondence from 1927-1937; statement of Produce Exchange president H.L. Bodman at the opening of the Bonded Grain Futures Market; a publicity booklet about the market (7 copies); rules regulating the grain futures trade for delivery in Buffalo among the Produce Exchange members (as amended to 1931); and the certificate of incorporation and by-laws of the New York Grain Clearing Corporation.
- Historical notes, undated (Offsite-box 1, Folder 13)
  Handwritten notes by W.G. Black, a historian of the Produce Exchange. The specific topic is unclear but appears to relate to a John Williams. The document is fragmenting; a photocopy is included in the folder.
- Report of delegation of the Produce Exchange to inspect the new barge canal, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 14)
  8 copies of the report, dated November 25, 1914, as reprinted from the January 1915 issue of "Flour, Hay, Grain & Feed"